[
    {
        "question": "Which animals are in the big 5?",
        "expected": "lion, leopard, black rhinoceros, African bush elephant, African buffalo, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animals do not have a spine?",
        "expected": "Invertebrates, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animals do not have a spine?",
        "expected": "Invertebrates, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which color is an elephant?",
        "expected": "grey, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent is the wombat endemic to?",
        "expected": "Australia, "
    },
    {
        "question": "In which habitat do tulips grow best?",
        "expected": "dry soil, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which awards did rosemary receive?",
        "expected": "Medicinal plant of the year 2000, Medicinal plant of the year 2011, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which colours can foxes be?",
        "expected": "black, orange, yellow, brown, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which tree produces papayas?",
        "expected": "Carica papaya, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Taxus is the Latin name for which tree?",
        "expected": "yew, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which tree was the winner of Austria's 2005 tree of the year award?",
        "expected": "The maple tree, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fruit type does a daisy (bellis perennis) have?",
        "expected": "achene, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which plant was the medicinal plant of the year in 2013?",
        "expected": "Rosa Ã— damascena, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which plant was the tree of the year in 2008?",
        "expected": "Juglans regia, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which cow lived the longest?",
        "expected": "Big Bertha, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which colours can the fruit of the apple tree have?",
        "expected": "red, yellow, green, pink, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which are the components of a flower?",
        "expected": "gynoecium, androecium, perianth, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which parts constitute a flower?",
        "expected": "gynoecium, androecium, perianth, "
    },
    {
        "question": "In which habitats do giraffes live?",
        "expected": "Savanna, woodland, "
    },
    {
        "question": "To which genus does a rose belong?",
        "expected": "Rosa cinnamomea, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which color is a fox?",
        "expected": "black, orange, yellow, brown, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which color are sunflowers?",
        "expected": "yellow, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which plant is saffron made of?",
        "expected": "Crocus sativus, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which species of dolphins is self-aware?",
        "expected": "Bottlenose dolphin, "
    },
    {
        "question": "After which country is the fruit 'orange' named in Turkish language?",
        "expected": "Portugal, "
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the Old Tjikko tree located?",
        "expected": "Sweden, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which species of mammal is considered the largest land animal?",
        "expected": "African bush elephant, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is platypus endemic to?",
        "expected": "Australia, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which bird has the largests wingspan?",
        "expected": "Albatross, "
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country the International Plant Names Index is based?",
        "expected": "United Kingdom, "
    },
    {
        "question": "To which subclass does the elephant belong?",
        "expected": "mammal, "
    },
    {
        "question": "To which family did mammoths belong?",
        "expected": "Elephantidae, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Of which plant classes is birch a subclass?",
        "expected": "tree, shrub, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of fruit do rubber trees produce?",
        "expected": "capsule, "
    }
]